[Music]
Lut, I have been hearing this since childhood, who has
seen tomorrow Today for the first time I am feeling it
Who would have thought that I would have to think twice before leaving the house Forget
hugging, even shaking hands would be
difficult Someone shouting God bless us were
welcoming guests This will bring
knowledge and science The faces of superheroes will fall
I had thought in this Who would have thought that
rockstars would emerge from there Now
that Gandhians will learn internet and doodles on cooking
We will restore the status of our loved ones We will
value our life so much That we will not
think about tomorrow but from today When something is priceless, we do
n't take any chances It has happened
[Music] That's why it is for
you
ICICI Prudential Life
Kraft Smart All in One Temple Run Tomorrow or
today We will see
Ajay